let data = [
	{
	  "elementName": "Hydrogen",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Hydrogen",
			"answer": 1
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hydrogen's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hydrogen's abbreviation",
			"answer": "H"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Hydrogen or Arsenic?",
			"answer": "Hydrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Hydrogen",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hydrogen's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hydrogen's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Hydrogen or Oxygen?",
			"answer": "Hydrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Hydrogen",
			"answer": 0
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Helium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Helium",
			"answer": 2
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Helium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Helium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "He"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Helium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "0"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Helium",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Helium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Helium or Radon?",
			"answer": "Helium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Helium",
			"answer": "2"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Lithium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Lithium",
			"answer": 3
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lithium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lithium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Li"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Lithium or Hydrogen?",
			"answer": "Hydrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Lithium",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lithium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lithium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Lithium or Lutetium",
			"answer": "Lutetium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Lithium",
			"answer": 4
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Beryllium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Beryllium",
			"answer": 4
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Beryllium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Beryllium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Be"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Beryllium or Promethium?",
			"answer": "Beryllium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Beryllium",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Beryllium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Beryllium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Beryllium or Zinc",
			"answer": "Zinc"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Beryllium",
			"answer": 5
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Boron",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Boron",
			"answer": 5
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Boron's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Boron's abbreviation",
			"answer": "B"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Boron or Ruthenium?",
			"answer": "Ruthenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Boron",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Boron's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Boron's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Boron or Silicon",
			"answer": "Boron"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Boron",
			"answer": 6
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Carbon",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Carbon",
			"answer": 6
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Carbon's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Carbon's abbreviation",
			"answer": "C"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Carbon or Beryllium?",
			"answer": "Carbon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Carbon",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Carbon's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Carbon's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Carbon or Nitrogen",
			"answer": "Nitrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Carbon",
			"answer": 6
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Nitrogen",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Nitrogen",
			"answer": 7
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nitrogen's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nitrogen's abbreviation",
			"answer": "N"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Nitrogen or Cesium?",
			"answer": "Nitrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Nitrogen",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nitrogen's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nitrogen's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Nitrogen or Krypton",
			"answer": "Nitrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Nitrogen",
			"answer": 7
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Oxygen",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Oxygen",
			"answer": 8
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oxygen's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oxygen's abbreviation",
			"answer": "O"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Oxygen or Astatine?",
			"answer": "Oxygen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Oxygen",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oxygen's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oxygen's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Oxygen or Argon",
			"answer": "Argon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Oxygen",
			"answer": 8
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Fluorine",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Fluorine",
			"answer": 9
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fluorine's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fluorine's abbreviation",
			"answer": "F"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Fluorine or Bismuth?",
			"answer": "Fluorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Fluorine",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fluorine's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fluorine's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Fluorine or Helium",
			"answer": "Helium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Fluorine",
			"answer": 10
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Neon",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Neon",
			"answer": 10
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neon's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neon's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ne"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neon's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "0"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Neon",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neon's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Neon or Iodine",
			"answer": "Neon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Neon",
			"answer": "10"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Sodium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Sodium",
			"answer": 11
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sodium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sodium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Na"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Sodium or Lithium?",
			"answer": "Sodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Sodium",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sodium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sodium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Sodium or Lawrencium",
			"answer": "Sodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Sodium",
			"answer": 12
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Magnesium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Magnesium",
			"answer": 12
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Magnesium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Magnesium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Mg"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Magnesium or Rhodium?",
			"answer": "Rhodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Magnesium",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Magnesium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Magnesium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Magnesium or Copper",
			"answer": "Copper"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Magnesium",
			"answer": 12
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Aluminum",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Aluminum",
			"answer": 13
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Aluminum 's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Aluminum 's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Al"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Aluminum or Erbium?",
			"answer": "Aluminum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Aluminum",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Aluminum's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Aluminum's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Aluminum or Americium",
			"answer": "Aluminum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Aluminum",
			"answer": 14
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Silicon",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Silicon",
			"answer": 14
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silicon 's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silicon 's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Si"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Silicon or Nitrogen?",
			"answer": "Nitrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Silicon",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silicon's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silicon's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Silicon or Palladium",
			"answer": "Palladium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Silicon",
			"answer": 14
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Phosphorus",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Phosphorus",
			"answer": 15
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Phosphorus 's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Phosphorus 's abbreviation",
			"answer": "P"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Phosphorus or Mendelevium?",
			"answer": "Phosphorus"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Phosphorus",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Phosphorus's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Phosphorus's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Phosphorus or Iodine",
			"answer": "Phosphorus"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Phosphorus",
			"answer": 16
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Sulfur",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Sulfur",
			"answer": 16
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sulfur 's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sulfur's abbreviation",
			"answer": "S"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Sulfur or Ytterbium?",
			"answer": "Sulfur"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Sulfur",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sulfur's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Sulfur's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Sulfur or Zinc",
			"answer": "Sulfur"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Sulfur",
			"answer": 16
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Chlorine",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Chlorine",
			"answer": 17
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chlorine 's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chlorine's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cl"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Chlorine or Molybdenum?",
			"answer": "Chlorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Chlorine",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chlorine's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chlorine's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Chlorine or Xenon",
			"answer": "Chlorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Chlorine",
			"answer": 18
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Argon",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Argon",
			"answer": 18
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Argon's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Argon's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ar"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Argon",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Argon's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "0"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Argon's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Argon or Fluorine",
			"answer": "Fluorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Argon",
			"answer": "22"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Potassium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Potassium",
			"answer": 19
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Potassium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Potassium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "K"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Potassium or Calcium?",
			"answer": "Calcium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Potassium",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Potassium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Potassium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Potassium or Francium",
			"answer": "Potassium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Potassium",
			"answer": 20
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Calcium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Calcium",
			"answer": 20
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Calcium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Calcium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ca"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Calcium or Scandium?",
			"answer": "Scandium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Calcium",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Calcium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Calcium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Calcium or Gadolinium",
			"answer": "Gadolinium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Calcium",
			"answer": 20
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Scandium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Scandium",
			"answer": 21
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Scandiums State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Scandium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Sc"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Scandium or Osmium?",
			"answer": "Osmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Scandium",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Scandium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Scandium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Scandium or Fermium",
			"answer": "Scandium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Scandium",
			"answer": 24
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Titanium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Titanium",
			"answer": 22
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Titanium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Titanium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ti"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Titanium or Sodium?",
			"answer": "Titanium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Titanium",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Titanium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Titanium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Titanium or Hafnium",
			"answer": "Titanium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Titanium",
			"answer": 26
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Vanadium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Vanadium",
			"answer": 23
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Vanadium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Vanadium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "V"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Vanadium or Calcium?",
			"answer": "Vanadium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Vanadium",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Vanadium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Vanadium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Vanadium or Nobelium",
			"answer": "Vanadium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Vanadium",
			"answer": 28
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Chromium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Chromium",
			"answer": 24
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chromium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chromium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Chromium or Cobalt?",
			"answer": "Cobalt"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Chromium",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chromium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Chromium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1))",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Ruthenium or Chromium",
			"answer": "Ruthenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Chromium",
			"answer": 28
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Manganese",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Manganese",
			"answer": 25
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Manganese's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Manganese's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Mn"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Manganese or Chromium?",
			"answer": "Chromium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Manganese",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Maganese's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Maganese's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Thorium or Manganese",
			"answer": "Manganese"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Manganese",
			"answer": 30
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Iron",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Iron",
			"answer": 26
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iron's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iron's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Fe"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Iron or Rubidium?",
			"answer": "Iron"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Iron",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iron's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element.",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iron's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Fluorine or Iron?",
			"answer": "Fluorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Iron",
			"answer": 30
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Cobalt",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Cobalt",
			"answer": 27
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cobalt's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cobalt's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Co"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Cobalt or Gallium?",
			"answer": "Cobalt"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Cobalt",
			"answer": "9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cobalt's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cobalt's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Thallium or Cobalt",
			"answer": "Cobalt"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Cobalt",
			"answer": 32
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Nickel",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Nickel",
			"answer": 28
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nickel's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nickel's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ni"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Nickel or Iron?",
			"answer": "Nickel"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Nickel",
			"answer": "10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nickel's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nickel's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Einsteinium or Nickel?",
			"answer": "Nickel"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Nickel",
			"answer": 31
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Copper",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Copper",
			"answer": 29
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copper's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copper's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cu"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Copper or Calcium?",
			"answer": "Copper"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Copper",
			"answer": "11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copper's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copper's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Germanium or Copper?",
			"answer": "Germanium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Copper",
			"answer": 35
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Zinc",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Zinc",
			"answer": 30
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zinc's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zinc's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Zn"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Zinc or Chlorine?",
			"answer": "Chlorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Zinc",
			"answer": "12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zinc's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zinc's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Nobelium or Zinc?",
			"answer": "Zinc"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Zinc",
			"answer": 35
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Gallium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Gallium",
			"answer": 31
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gallium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gallium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ga"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Gallium or Zirconium?",
			"answer": "Gallium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Gallium",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gallium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gallium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Iridium or Gallium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Gallium",
			"answer": 39
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Germanium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Germanium",
			"answer": 32
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Germanium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Germanium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ge"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Germanium or Krypton?",
			"answer": "Krypton"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Germanium",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Germanium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Germanium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Lawrencium or Germanium?",
			"answer": "Germanium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Germanium",
			"answer": 41
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Arsenic",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Arsenic",
			"answer": 33
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Arsenic's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Arsenic's abbreviation",
			"answer": "As"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Arsenic or Germanium?",
			"answer": "Arsenic"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Arsenic",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Arsenic's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Arsenic's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Hafnium or Arsenic?",
			"answer": "Arsenic"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Arsenic",
			"answer": 42
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Selenium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Selenium",
			"answer": 34
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Selenium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Selenium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Se"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Selenium or Ruthenium?",
			"answer": "Selenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Selenium",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Selenium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Selenium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Fermium or Selenium?",
			"answer": "Selenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Selenium",
			"answer": 45
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Bromine",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Bromine",
			"answer": 35
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bromine's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "liquid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bromine's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Br"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Bromine or Chromium?",
			"answer": "Bromine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Bromine",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bromine's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bromine's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Tungsten or Bromine?",
			"answer": "Bromine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Bromine",
			"answer": 45
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Krypton",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Krypton",
			"answer": 36
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Krypton's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "liquid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Krypton's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Kr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Krypton or Lutetium?",
			"answer": "Krypton"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Krypton.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Krypton's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "0"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Krypton's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Iodine or Krypton?",
			"answer": "Krypton"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Krypton",
			"answer": 48
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Rubidium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Rubidium",
			"answer": 37
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rubidium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rubidium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Rb"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Rubidium or Nickel?",
			"answer": "Nickel"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Rubidium.",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rubidium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rubidium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Niobium or Rubidium?",
			"answer": "Niobium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Rubidium",
			"answer": 48
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Strontium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Strontium",
			"answer": 37
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Strontium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Strontium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Sr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Strontium or Fermium?",
			"answer": "Fermium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Strontium.",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Strontium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Strontium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Actinium or Strontium?",
			"answer": "Strontium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Strontium",
			"answer": 50
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Yttrium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Yttrium",
			"answer": 39
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Yttrium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Yttrium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Y"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Yttrium or Strontium?",
			"answer": "Yttrium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Yttrium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Yttrium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Yttrium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Fermium or Yttrium?",
			"answer": "Fermium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Yttrium",
			"answer": 50
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Zirconium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Zirconium",
			"answer": 40
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zirconium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zirconium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Zr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Zirconium or Germanium?",
			"answer": "Germanium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Zirconium.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zirocnium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Zirocnium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Fermium or Zirconium?",
			"answer": "Zirconium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Zirconium",
			"answer": 51
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Niobium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Niobium",
			"answer": 41
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Niobium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Niobium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Nb"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Niobium or Scandium?",
			"answer": "Niobium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Niobium.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Niobium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Niobium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Plutonium or Niobium?",
			"answer": "Niobium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Niobium",
			"answer": 52
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Molybdenum",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Molybdenum",
			"answer": 42
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Molybdenum's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Molybdenum's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Mo"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Molybdenum or Krypton?",
			"answer": "Krypton"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Molybdenum.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Molybdenum's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Molybdenum's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Xenon or Molybdenum?",
			"answer": "Xenon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Molybdenum",
			"answer": 54
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Technetium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Technetium",
			"answer": 43
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Technetium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Technetium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Tc"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Technetium or Hydrogen?",
			"answer": "Technetium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Technetium.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Technetium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Technetium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^2 4d^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Polonium or Technetium?",
			"answer": "Polonium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Technetium",
			"answer": 55
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Ruthenium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Ruthenium",
			"answer": 44
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ruthenium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ruthenium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ru"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Ruthenium or Antimony?",
			"answer": "Ruthenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Ruthenium.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ruthenium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ruthenium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Polonium or Technetium?",
			"answer": "Ruthenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Ruthenium",
			"answer": 57
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Rhodium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Rhodium",
			"answer": 45
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhodium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhodium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Rh"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Rhodium or Palladium?",
			"answer": "Palladium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Rhodium.",
			"answer": "9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhodium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhodium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Mendelevium or Rhodium?",
			"answer": "Rhodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Rhodium",
			"answer": 58
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Palladium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Palladium",
			"answer": 46
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Palladium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Palladium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pd"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Palladium or Selenium?",
			"answer": "Selenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Palladium.",
			"answer": "10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Palladium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Palladium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 4d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Californium or Palladium?",
			"answer": "Palladium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Palladium",
			"answer": 60
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Silver",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Silver",
			"answer": 47
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silver's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silver's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ag"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Silver or Osmium?",
			"answer": "Osmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Silver.",
			"answer": "11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silver's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Silver's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Helium or Silver?",
			"answer": "Helium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Silver",
			"answer": 61
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Cadmium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Cadmium",
			"answer": 48
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cadmium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cadmium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cd"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Cadmium or Cerium?",
			"answer": "Cadmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Cadmium.",
			"answer": "12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cadmium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cadmium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^2 4d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Radon or Cadmium?",
			"answer": "Radon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Cadmium",
			"answer": 64
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Indium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Indium",
			"answer": 49
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Indium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Indium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "In"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Indium or Tin?",
			"answer": "Tin"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Indium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Indium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Indium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Fluorine or Indium?",
			"answer": "Fluorine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Indium",
			"answer": 66
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Tin",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Tin",
			"answer": 50
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tin's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tin's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Sn"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Tin or Cerium?",
			"answer": "Tin"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Tin.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tin's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tin's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Platinum or Tin?",
			"answer": "Platinum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Tin",
			"answer": 69
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Antimony",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Antimony",
			"answer": 51
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Antimony's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Antimony's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Sb"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Antimony or Cesium?",
			"answer": "Antimony"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Antimony.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Antimony's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Antimony's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Californium or Antimony?",
			"answer": "Antimony"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Antimony",
			"answer": 71
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Tellurium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Tellurium",
			"answer": 52
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tellurium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tellurium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Te"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Tellurium or Sodium?",
			"answer": "Tellurium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Tellurium.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tellirum's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tellirum's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Astatine or Tellurium?",
			"answer": "Astatine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Tellurium",
			"answer": 76
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Iodine",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Iodine",
			"answer": 53
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iodine's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iodine's abbreviation",
			"answer": "I"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Iodine or Platinum?",
			"answer": "Iodine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Iodine.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iodine's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iodine's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Thorium or Iodine?",
			"answer": "Iodine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Iodine",
			"answer": 74
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Xenon",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Xenon",
			"answer": 54
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Xenon's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Xenon's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Xe"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Xenon or Sulfur?",
			"answer": "Xenon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Neon.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Xeneon's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "0"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Xeneon's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Hydrogen or Xenon?",
			"answer": "Hydrogen"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Xenon",
			"answer": 77
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Cesium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Cesium",
			"answer": 55
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cesium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cesium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cs"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Cesium or Hafnium?",
			"answer": "Hafnium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Cesium.",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cesium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cesium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Zinc or Cesium?",
			"answer": "Zinc"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Cesium",
			"answer": 78
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Barium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Barium",
			"answer": 56
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Barium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Barium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ba"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Barium or Californium?",
			"answer": "Californium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Barium.",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Barium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Barium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Mercury or Barium?",
			"answer": "Mercury"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Barium",
			"answer": 81
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Lanthanum",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Lanthanum",
			"answer": 57
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lanthanum's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lanthanum's abbreviation",
			"answer": "La"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Lanthanum or Rhodium?",
			"answer": "Rhodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Lanthanum.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lanthanum's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lanthanum's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 5d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Gold or Lanthanum?",
			"answer": "Gold"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Lanthanum",
			"answer": 82
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Cerium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Cerium",
			"answer": 58
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cerium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cerium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ce"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Cerium or Iridium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Cerium.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cerium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Cerium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 5d^1 4f^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Terbium or Cerium?",
			"answer": "Terbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Cerium",
			"answer": 82
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Praseodymium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Praseodymium",
			"answer": 59
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Praseodymium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Praseodymium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Praseodymium or Copper?",
			"answer": "Copper"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Praseodymium.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Praseodymium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Praseodymium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Lutetium or Praseodymium?",
			"answer": "Praseodymium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Praseodymium",
			"answer": 82
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Neodymium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Neodymium",
			"answer": 60
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neodymium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neodymium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Nd"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Neodymium or Xenon?",
			"answer": "Xenon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Neodymium.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neodymium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neodymium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Thorium or Neodymium?",
			"answer": "Thorium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Neodymium",
			"answer": 84
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Promethium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Promethium",
			"answer": 61
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Promethium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Promethium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pm"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Promethium or Rhodium?",
			"answer": "Rhodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Promethium.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Promethium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Promethium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Osmium or Promethium?",
			"answer": "Osmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Promethium",
			"answer": 84
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Samarium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Samarium",
			"answer": 62
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Samarium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Samarium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Sm"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Samarium or Mercury?",
			"answer": "Mercury"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Samarium.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Samarium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Samarium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Osmium or Samarium?",
			"answer": "Osmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Samarium",
			"answer": 88
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Europium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Europium",
			"answer": 63
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Europium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Europium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Eu"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Europium or Vanadium?",
			"answer": "Vanadium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Europium.",
			"answer": "9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Europium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Europium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Polonium or Europium?",
			"answer": "Polonium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Europium",
			"answer": 89
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Gadolinium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Gadolinium",
			"answer": 64
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gadolinium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gadolinium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Gd"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Gadolinium or Neodymium?",
			"answer": "Gadolinium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Gadolinium.",
			"answer": "10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gadolinium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gadolinium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^75d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Polonium or Gadolinium?",
			"answer": "Polonium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Gadolinium",
			"answer": 93
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Terbium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Terbium",
			"answer": 65
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Terbium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Terbium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Tb"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Terbium or Thulium?",
			"answer": "Thulium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Terbium.",
			"answer": "11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Terbium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Terbium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Indium or Terbium?",
			"answer": "Terbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Terbium",
			"answer": 94
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Dysprosium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Dysprosium",
			"answer": 66
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dysprosium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dysprosium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Dy"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Dysprosium or Ytterbium?",
			"answer": "Ytterbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Dysprosium.",
			"answer": "12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dysprosium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dysprosium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Thulium or Dysprosium?",
			"answer": "Thulium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Dysprosium",
			"answer": 97
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Holmium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Holmium",
			"answer": 67
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Holmium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Holmium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ho"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Holmium or Rhodium?",
			"answer": "Rhodium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Holmium.",
			"answer": "13"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Holmium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Holmium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Irdium or Holmium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Holmium",
			"answer": 98
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Erbium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Erbium",
			"answer": 68
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Erbium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Erbium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Er"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Erbium or Promethium?",
			"answer": "Erbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Erbium.",
			"answer": "14"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Erbium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Erbium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Mendelevium or Erbium?",
			"answer": "Mendelevium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Erbium",
			"answer": 99
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Thulium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Thulium",
			"answer": 69
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thulium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thulium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Tm"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Thulium or Sodium?",
			"answer": "Thulium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Thulium.",
			"answer": "15"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thulium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thulium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^13"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Uranium or Thulium?",
			"answer": "Uranium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Thulium",
			"answer": 100
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Ytterbium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Ytterbium",
			"answer": 70
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ytterbium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ytterbium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Yb"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Ytterbium or Tungsten?",
			"answer": "Ytterbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Ytterbium.",
			"answer": "16"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ytterbium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ytterbium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Curium or Ytterbium?",
			"answer": "Ytterbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Ytterbium",
			"answer": 103
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Lutetium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Lutetium",
			"answer": 71
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lutetium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lutetium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Lu"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Lutetium or Dysprosium?",
			"answer": "Lutetium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Lutetium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lutetium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lutetium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Radium or Lutetium?",
			"answer": "Lutetium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Lutetium",
			"answer": 104
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Hafnium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Hafnium",
			"answer": 72
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hafnium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hafnium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Hf"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Hafnium or Thulium?",
			"answer": "Hafnium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Hafnium.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hafnium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hafnium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Iridium or Hafnium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Hafnium",
			"answer": 106
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Tantalum",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Tantalum",
			"answer": 73
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tantalum's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tantalum's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ta"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Tantalum or Magnesium?",
			"answer": "Tantalum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Tantalum.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tantalum's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tantalum's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Platnium  or Tantalum?",
			"answer": "Platinum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Tantalum",
			"answer": 108
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Tungsten",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Tungsten",
			"answer": 74
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tungsten's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tungsten's abbreviation",
			"answer": "W"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Tungsten or Krypton?",
			"answer": "Krypton"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Tungsten.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tungsten's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tungsten's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Francium or Tungsten?",
			"answer": "Tungsten"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Tungsten",
			"answer": 110
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Rhenium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Rhenium",
			"answer": 75
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhenium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhenium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Re"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Rhenium or Aluminum?",
			"answer": "Rhenium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Rhenium.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhenium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rhenium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Astatine or Rhenium?",
			"answer": "Astatine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Rhenium",
			"answer": 111
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Osmium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Osmium",
			"answer": 76
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Osmium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Osmium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Os"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Osmium or Ytterbium?",
			"answer": "Osmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Osmium.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Osmium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Osmium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Iridium or Osmium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Osmium",
			"answer": 114
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Iridium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Iridium",
			"answer": 77
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iridium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Iridium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ir"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Iridium or Thallium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Iridium.",
			"answer": "9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Irdium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Irdium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Lawrencium or Iridium?",
			"answer": "Iridium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Iridium",
			"answer": 115
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Platinum",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Platinum",
			"answer": 77
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Platinum's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Platinum's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pt"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Platinum or Tin?",
			"answer": "Platinum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Platinum.",
			"answer": "10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Platinum's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Platinum's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Cadmium or Platinum?",
			"answer": "Cadmium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Platinum",
			"answer": 117
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Gold",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Gold",
			"answer": 79
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gold's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gold's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Au"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Gold or Niobium?",
			"answer": "Gold"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Gold.",
			"answer": "11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gold's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Gold's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Cobalt or Gold?",
			"answer": "Gold"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Gold",
			"answer": 118
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Mercury",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Mercury",
			"answer": 80
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mercury's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "liquid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mercury's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Au"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Mercury or Chromium?",
			"answer": "Mercury"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Mercury.",
			"answer": "12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mercury's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mercury's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Thorium or Mercury?",
			"answer": "Mercury"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Mercury",
			"answer": 121
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Thallium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Thallium",
			"answer": 81
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thallium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thallium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Tl"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Thallium or Praseodymium?",
			"answer": "Thallium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Thallium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thallium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thallium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Erbium or Thallium?",
			"answer": "Erbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Thallium",
			"answer": 123
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Lead",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Lead",
			"answer": 82
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lead's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lead's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pb"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Lead or Bismuth?",
			"answer": "Lead"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Lead.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lead's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lead's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Uranium or Lead?",
			"answer": "Lead"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Lead",
			"answer": 125
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Bismuth",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Bismuth",
			"answer": 83
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bismuth's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bismuth's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Bi"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Bismuth or Fancium?",
			"answer": "Bismuth"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Bismuth.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bismuth's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bismuth's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Lead or Bismuth?",
			"answer": "Lead"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Bismuth",
			"answer": 126
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Polonium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Polonium",
			"answer": 84
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Polonium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Polonium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Po"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Polonium or Thorium?",
			"answer": "Polonium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Polonium.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Polonium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Polonium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Francium or Polonium?",
			"answer": "Polonium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Polonium",
			"answer": 125
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Astatine",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Astatine",
			"answer": 85
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Astatine's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Astatine's abbreviation",
			"answer": "At"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Astatine or Cobalt?",
			"answer": "Astatine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Astatine.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Astatine's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "-1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Astatine's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Actinium or Astatine?",
			"answer": "Astatine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Astatine",
			"answer": 125
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Radon",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Radon",
			"answer": 86
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radon's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "gas"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radon's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Rn"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Radon.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radon's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "0"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radon's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Curium or Radon?",
			"answer": "Radon"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Radon",
			"answer": "136"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Francium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Francium",
			"answer": 87
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Francium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Francium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Fr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Francium or Europium?",
			"answer": "Europium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Francium.",
			"answer": "1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Francium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Francium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^6 7s^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Helium or Francium?",
			"answer": "Helium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Francium",
			"answer": 136
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Radium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Radium",
			"answer": 88
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ra"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Radium or Manganese?",
			"answer": "Manganese"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Radium.",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Radium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^6 7s^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Lithium or Radium?",
			"answer": "Lithium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Radium",
			"answer": 138
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Actinium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Actinium",
			"answer": 89
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Actinium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Actinium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ac"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Actinium or Fermium?",
			"answer": "1.1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Actinium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Actinium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Actinium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^6 7s^2 6d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Plutonium or Actinium?",
			"answer": "Plutonium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Actinium",
			"answer": 138
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Thorium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Thorium",
			"answer": 90
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thorium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thorium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Th"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Thorium or Promethium?",
			"answer": "Thorium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Thorium.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thorium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Thorium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^6 7s^2 6d^2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Fermium or Thorium?",
			"answer": "Fermium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Thorium",
			"answer": 142
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Protactinium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Protactinium",
			"answer": 91
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Protactinium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Protactinium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pa"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Protactinium or Uranium?",
			"answer": "Protactinium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Protactinium.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Protactinium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Protactinium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^2 6d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Nobelium or Protactinium?",
			"answer": "Nobelium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Protactinium",
			"answer": 140
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Uranium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Uranium",
			"answer": 92
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Uranium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Uranium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "U"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Uranium or Iodine?",
			"answer": "Iodine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Uranium.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Uranium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Uranium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^3 6d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Mendelevium or Uranium?",
			"answer": "Mendelevium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Uranium",
			"answer": 146
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Neptunium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Neptunium",
			"answer": 93
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neptunium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neptunium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Np"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Neptunium or Fermium?",
			"answer": "Neptunium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Neptunium.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neptunium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Neptunium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^4 6d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Neptunium or Aluminum?",
			"answer": "Neptunium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Neptunium",
			"answer": 144
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Plutonium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Plutonium",
			"answer": 94
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Plutonium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Plutonium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Pu"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Plutonium or Sulfur?",
			"answer": "Sulfur"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Plutonium.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Plutonium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Plutonium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Erbium or Plutonium?",
			"answer": "Erbium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Plutonium",
			"answer": 148
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Americium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Americium",
			"answer": 95
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Americium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Americium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Am"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Americium or Cerium?",
			"answer": "Americium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Americium.",
			"answer": "9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Americium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Americium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Aluminum or Americium?",
			"answer": "Aluminum"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Americium",
			"answer": 148
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Curium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Curium",
			"answer": 96
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Curium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Curium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cm"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Curium or Astatine?",
			"answer": "Astatine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Curium.",
			"answer": "10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Curium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Curium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^7 6d^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Gallium or Curium?",
			"answer": "Gallium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Curium",
			"answer": 151
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Berkelium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Berkelium",
			"answer": 97
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Berkelium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Berkelium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Bk"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Berkelium or Iodine?",
			"answer": "Iodine"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Berkelium.",
			"answer": "11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Berkelium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Berkelium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Uranium or Berkelium?",
			"answer": "Berkelium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Berkelium",
			"answer": 150
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Californium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Californium",
			"answer": 98
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Californium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Californium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cf"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Californium or Tungsten?",
			"answer": "Tungsten"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Californium.",
			"answer": "12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Californium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Californium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Neptunium or Californium?",
			"answer": "Neptunium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Californium",
			"answer": 153
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Einsteinium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Einsteinium",
			"answer": 99
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Einsteinium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Einsteinium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Es"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Einstenium or Phosphorus?",
			"answer": "Phosphorus"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Ensteinium.",
			"answer": "13"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Ensteinium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Enstenium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy Radium or Ensteinium?",
			"answer": "Ensteinium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Einsteinium",
			"answer": 153
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Fermium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Fermium",
			"answer": 100
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fermium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fermium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Fm"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Fermium or Mercury?",
			"answer": "Mercury"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Fermium.",
			"answer": "14"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fermium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Fermium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy:  Nobelium or Fermium?",
			"answer": "Nobelium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Fermium",
			"answer": 157
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Mendelevium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Mendelevium",
			"answer": 101
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mendelevium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mendelevium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Md"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Mendelevium or Beryllium?",
			"answer": "Beryllium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Mendelevium.",
			"answer": "15"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mendelevium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Mendelevium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^13"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Nobelium or Mendelevium?",
			"answer": "Nobelium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Mendelevium",
			"answer": 157
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Nobelium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Nobelium",
			"answer": 102
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nobelium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nobelium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "No"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher Electronegativity:  Nobelium or Antimony?",
			"answer": "Antimony"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Nobelium.",
			"answer": "16"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nobelium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nobelium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Scandium or Nobelium?",
			"answer": "Nobelium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Nobelium",
			"answer": 148
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Lawrencium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Lawrencium",
			"answer": 103
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lawrencium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lawrencium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Lr"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Lawrencium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lawrencium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Lawrencium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 7p^1"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Which element has a higher ionization energy: Potassium or Lawrencium?",
			"answer": "Lawerncium"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "What is the neutron number for Lawrencium",
			"answer": "157"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Rutherfordium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Rutherfordium",
			"answer": 104
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rutherfordium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rutherfordium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Rf"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Rutherfordium.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rutherfordium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Rutherfordium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^2"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Dubnium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Dubnium",
			"answer": 105
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dubnium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dubnium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Db"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Dubnium.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dubnium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Dubnium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^3"
		 }
   
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Seaborgium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Seaborgium",
			"answer": 106
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Seaborgium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Seaborgium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Sg"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Seaborgium.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Seaborgium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Seaborgium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^4"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Bohrium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Bohrium",
			"answer": 107
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bohrium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bohrium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Bh"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Bohrium.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bohrium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Bohrium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^5"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Hassium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Hassium",
			"answer": 108
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hassium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hassium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Hs"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Hassium.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hassium's oxidation state that makes the outer shell of itself 'full' when combined with another element",
			"answer": "+8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Hassium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^6"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Meitnerium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Meitnerium",
			"answer": 109
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Meitnerium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Meitnerium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Mt"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Meitnerium.",
			"answer": "9"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Meitnerium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^7"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Darmstadtium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Darmstadtium",
			"answer": 110
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Darmstadtium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Darmstadtium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ds"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Darmstadtium.",
			"answer": "10"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Darmstadtium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^8"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Roentgenium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Roentgenium",
			"answer": 111
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Roentgenium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Roentgenium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Rg"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Roentgenium.",
			"answer": "11"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Roentgenium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^9"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Copernicium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Copernicium",
			"answer": 112
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copernicium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "liquid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copernicium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Cn"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Copernicium.",
			"answer": "12"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Copernicium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Nihonium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Nihonium",
			"answer": 113
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nihonium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nihonium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Nh"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Nihonium.",
			"answer": "3"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Nihonium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10 7p^1"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Flerovium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Flerovium",
			"answer": 114
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Flerovium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Flerovium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Fl"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Flerovium.",
			"answer": "4"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Flerovium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10 7p^2"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Moscovium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Moscovium",
			"answer": 115
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Moscovium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Moscovium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Mc"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Moscovium.",
			"answer": "5"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Moscovium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10 7p^3"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Livermorium",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Livermorium",
			"answer": 116
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Livermorium's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Livermorium's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Lv"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Livermorium.",
			"answer": "6"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Livermorium's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10 7p^4"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Tennessine",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Tennessine",
			"answer": 117
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tennessine's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tennessine's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Ts"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Tennessine.",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Tennessine's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10 7p^5"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "Oganesson",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "Number of protons in Oganesson",
			"answer": 118
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oganesson's State at room temperature",
			"answer": "solid"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oganesson's abbreviation",
			"answer": "Og"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Number of valence electrons in Oganesson.",
			"answer": "8"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "Oganesson's Electron Configuration. (When a number is being raised, use the character '^', like for  1s<sup>1</sup>, you would say 1s^1)",
			"answer": "1s^2 2s^2 2p^6 3s^2 3p^6 4s^2 3d^10 4p^6 5s^1 4d^10 5p^6 6s^2 4f^14 5d^10 6p^1 7s^2 5f^14 6d^10 7p^6"
		 }
	  ]
   },
	{
	  "elementName": "General Knowledge",
	  "questionAndPoints": [
		 {
			"question": "How many valence electrons do the alkali metals have?",
			"answer": 1
		 },
		 {
			"question": "How many valence electrons do the alkaline metals have?",
			"answer": "2"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "How many valence electrons do the halogens have?",
			"answer": "7"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "True or False? Noble gasses have full valence electron shells",
			"answer": "TRUE"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "True or False? Hydrogen is an alkali metal",
			"answer": "FALSE"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "True or False? Strontium is an alkaline metal",
			"answer": "TRUE"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "True or False? Irdium is a halogen",
			"answer": "FALSE"
		 },
		 {
			"question": "True or False? Helium is a Noble gas have full valence electron shells",
			"answer": "TRUE"
		 }
	  ]
	}
   ]
